Randa Alrsheed Alnoor

randaalrsheed4@gmail.com 01142994009 Maadi,Cairo
Summary:
I have 2 years of experience in social developing with Community schools international foundation on both operational and field implementation roles; I hold Aviation and Tecnology diploma with focus on Cabin Crew . In addition to extensive online studies on self-development, functional and social studies.
- Two years of experience in the leading group, experience in management, and two years' experience as interprator .
Professional experience
Teaching experience from (2015-2017)
- I worked as english teacher for Hope and Light Community Learning Center in Egypt.
- Coordinating with students' families to ensure receiving their fees receipt .
- Data Enter and IT teacher - Writing Report - Prepare monthly school activities.
-I worked as English teacher for El-Etihad School in Sudan.
Work Experience
K2 Resturant supervisor From (2016 – 2017)
-Follow up with the staff to ensure everything is done as planned.
- Trainer for new comers.
- HR assistant in a hotel.
-writing monthly reports.
Volunteering Experience
-Community mentor – Care From (May 2020 – October2018) .
- Community peer Aducator at Care Organization.
-Community Outreach- Tadamon Community Center.

- Contribute in distributing foot boxes, winter closes and blankets .

- Provide awareness workshops for refugees in Maadi during Covid-19.
Education
- Diploma of Aviation and Technology March 2013 – July2015.
-Sudanese High School -2012
Courses
- Data Analysis - Coursera;
- Execl to MYSQL-Coursera;
- English Language –Biritsh Institute;
- ICDL - Coursea
- First aid workshop- Sudanese Red Crescent Society